export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Do you accept cash or personal check payments?",
    answer:
      "Currently MarvCleaning does not accept cash or personal checks as a form of payment.However, we accept all major credit cards through our 100% secured 256-bit SSL protocol processed by Stripe via online payment.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "I have a question about my invoice. Who should I contact?",
    answer:
      "Please contact our customer service department for any payment inquires. You can contact us at (352)-306-4415 or send us an email to support@marvcleaning.com.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "I need to cancel or change my plan. What should I do?",
    answer:
      "Please contact our customer service department if you would like to cancel or change your current cleaning frequency. You can contact us at (352)-306-4415 or send us an email to support@marvcleaning.com.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "I have special instructions, what should I do?",
    answer:
      "When booking your appointment, you will have an option to write down any special instructions that you may have for the cleaner.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Do I need to tip the cleaners?",
    answer:
      "Tipping is not mandatory, but we would undoubtedly appreciate your gratitude if you decided to tip our service personnel for their exceptional service.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Can I tip in cash?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you have the option of tipping our service personnel in cash before they leave you home or through the tipping tab found on our website.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Do you provide supplies and cleaning products?",
    answer:
      "Yes, MarvCleaning provides proper equipment, cleaning products, and supplies necessary to have your home sparkly clean.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What if I want to use my own products?",
    answer:
      "If you would like our service personnel to use your own household products, please let us know prior to the appointment and leave the products on your kitchen counter.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Do you use eco-friendly cleaning products?",
    answer:
      "Yes absolutely we carry large selection of eco-friendly cleaning products in order to be able to accommodate every need and request of our clients.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "How long will my cleaning appointment take?",
    answer:
      "Your cleaning appointment time is subjective. It depends on the size of your residential or commercial area. In addition, to specific needs.",
  },
];
